visistat.com 2019-09-14

# KickFire Privacy Policy

Welcome to the VisiStat, Inc., doing business as KickFire ("KickFire") Privacy Policy, effective as of August 15, 2019. By accessing any and all pages on this website and all affiliated websites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We respect your privacy and take it seriously. So please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of this website means that you consent to KickFire's collection, use and disclosure of information we receive from or about you. This Privacy Policy is governed by this website's Terms of Use, including limitation of KickFire's liability to you, so please review them as well. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or KickFire's Terms of Use, you may not use this website.

KickFire may, from time to time, change this Privacy Policy so we also ask that you occasionally review it and always review it before providing new personally identifiable information as defined below. Each of these changes will take effect 30 days from the date on which it is first published on this website.

This website collects the following information from you:

We collect your personal data ("PD") and personally identifiable information ("PII") on this website only if you voluntarily share it with us. By PD and PII we mean that which could identify you as an individual. Examples of this are an individual's name, address, telephone number, billing information, credit card information, other personal contact information and e-mail address. PD also includes other information subject to and as defined under the European Union General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"). This may include online identifiers provided by their devices, applications, tools and protocols.

Here's what we do with it:

Our lawful use, copying, retention and disclosure of any information or data that is not PD or PII is not restricted or affected by this Privacy Policy.

PD and PII is treated differently. We may use it in conjunction with the reasons you sent it to us and may use, copy, retain and disclose it for other lawful purposes, including sharing it with our affiliates, associates and partners such as advertisers, linked sites and independent contractors except that we will not ever resell it unless in aggregate or similar form that does not identify you as an individual.

Erasure of PD:  
You may request erasure of your PD to the extent required under law, including without limitation Article 17 (1) of the GDPR. If you wish to do so, please contact us at [support@kickfire.com](mailto:support@kickfire.com?subject=Contact%20KickFire%20\(Support\)).

Cookies:  
We work with a service provider ("the Provider") to serve digital advertising to you. The Provider uses cookies to collect data about (1) your browsing activity on the KickFire website and other websites, which are clients of the Provider (2) your device and browser information, and (3) the online ads the Provider has served (or attempted to serve to you).

The Provider uses tracking cookies, which enables the Provider to identify your device when you move between different websites or mobile applications so that the Provider and KickFire can serve targeted KickFire advertising to you.

If you would like to block or delete cookies we use, most web browsers have settings that let you do so. Most browsers also let you accept or reject all cookies, accept only certain types of cookies and let you know when a site wants to use a cookie.
